mequoda.com 2019-06-30

# Mequoda Privacy Policy - Mequoda Daily

### **Overview:**

Mequoda Systems, LLC is committed to protecting and maintaining your privacy.  It is a privilege for us to be trusted with your personal information.  To receive full access to our services, we request that you provide us with information that is important to you.  Because of the nature of this information, we want to let you know about the information we collect, why we collect it, how we protect it and how you can access or change it.

This policy covers only the information collected by the mequoda.com domain and website.  Sites that link to or from our site are not covered by this policy.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every site that you visit.  To ensure your comfort with Mequoda, this policy is linked to every page where we ask for information on our site.  To change or access your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) please click the “Please Log In” link and go to the “My Account” page or email [customercare@mequoda.com](mailto:customercare@mequoda.com).

We are continually looking to improve our site and our services.  The principle behind this policy and our business is to only collect information with your knowledge and consent.

### **Information We Collect:**

This policy refers to all information collected on the mequoda.com domain and website.  When visiting mequoda.com, you are given the opportunity to receive services from us when you provide us with information about you.  When you register to receive these services, we collect a limited amount of Personally Identifiable Information from you including your first name, last name and email address.

### **How Information is Used:**

When you first register for services on mequoda.com, we ask for your first name, last name and email address.  We send you a welcome email that includes a temporary password and a link to the login page of the site.  At first login, we ask you to change your password and modify your email preferences – what email newsletters do you want to receive?  Going, forward you will receive newsletters of your selection that may cover important information about our site, services that we offer, information about your membership and other offers or promotions.

All information sent by email will come from mequoda.com.  If you are looking to unsubscribe from one or more of our email lists/newsletters, you may use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of each email that we send.  You may also reach us by phone (866-713-1005) or email ([customercare@mequoda.com](mailto:customercare@mequoda.com)).

Mequoda Systems, LLC does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.  All information on current and former subscribers is retained in our database solely for customer service and accounting purposes.

Mequoda Systems, LLC may occasionally send you surveys to help us better serve you.  If and when you choose to participate in these optional surveys, you may also receive special offers via email.  If you would rather not receive these special offers, simply email [customercare@mequoda.com](mailto:customercare@mequoda.com) to cancel at any time.  Information that you provide when participating in a survey will be handled in the same manner as Personally Identifiable Information.

### **Personally Identifiable Information:**

Mequoda Systems, LLC does not share Personally Identifiable Information with third parties without your permission.  Mequoda may partner with companies who wish to offer our services to their current customers, prospective customers, mailing list members and site visitors.  These companies offer our services under their brand name, and if you choose to sign up for our services under the brand name of our partner company, we may share Personally Identifiable Information with that company.  Every time you sign up for a service, on our site or a partner company’s site, we will notify you of the privacy policy and how you can opt-out of the services.

Additionally, you have the right to request that your user data be deleted.  For these requests, please email [customercare@mequoda.com](mailto:customercare@mequoda.com) and we will respond within 30 days.

### **Children’s Information:**

Mequoda Systems, LLC does not knowingly collect or maintain information on mequoda.com from children under the age of 13; no part of our website is structured to attract those under the age of thirteen.

### **Cookies:**

Cookies set by a website owner or service provider (in this case Mequoda Systems, LLC) are called “first party cookies”.  Cookies that are set by parties other than the website owner are called “third party cookies”.  Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website or service that you are using such as advertising, interactive content and analytics.  Third parties that set third party cookies have the ability to recognize your computer both when it visits the website or service in question and also when you visit other websites or services.

Mequoda.com uses first party cookies each time you visit the website.  These cookies are used to remember specific information that you have already entered.  This allows you to not need to log in each time you visit the website.  Mequoda does not use cookies to collect additional Personally Identifiable Information about you.

Occasionally, Mequoda Systems, LLC enters into contracts with carefully selected third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you or to assist us in our own marketing activities.  This includes providing us with analytic information and search engine optimization services.  Our contracts with third parties prohibit the third party from using your Personal Identifiable Information for any purpose beyond the purpose for which it was shared.

If you wish to not accept cookies from mequoda.com, you can configure your web browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being transmitted (from the website to your browser).  You can also manually delete all cookie files from your device’s browser.

### **IP Addresses & Tracking:**

Mequoda Systems, LLC collects your IP information when you visit mequoda.com.  We do this to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ behavior inside the site, determine which site referred users to us and gather general demographic information.  Additionally, we may use tracking technology to track the completion of transactions on mequoda.com utilizing our email broadcasting system.

### **Future use of  Personally Identifiable Information:**

Mequoda Systems, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy and Personally Identifiable Information.  However, if Mequoda Systems, LLC is ever acquired by another organization, all of our assets, including information we’ve gathered, become the property of the new owner.  If this happens, the new owner’s policies may override this Privacy Policy.  Also, if Mequoda Systems, LLC ever goes out of business, all its assets, including the information we have gathered, may be sold or dissolved.

If you have any questions or comments, please email Mequoda Systems Customer Service: [customercare@mequoda.com](mailto:customercare@mequoda.com).
